A gourmet rating to guess which is the most consistent food item and which is the most expensive.
Last time, we hit the fine grape juice and the fine cheese. There are only two items left, and if you get all the questions right, the channel will be renamed "The Sommelier Company," as you wish.
But if we get it wrong, we'll be labeled as taste geeks.
Wait... are they quitting on us?
We've been stopped.
I thought you were a tastemaker.
Entertain me.
Really?
You're lying for sure.
Next, I'm going to compare a loaf of bread from the supermarket with a loaf of expensive bread that costs 1,000 yen a loaf.
You can guess which one it is based on your reactions.
Are you confident?
I'm sure! I'm confident, too.
I eat a lot of expensive bread.
I like to go out and buy it on a regular basis.
Is it totally different?
No.
Most people eat bread for breakfast when they go to school.
It's a familiar bread.
You know what I mean?
Yes, I do.
Are you confident about it?
Yes! I'm confident enough.
What finger should I be holding out for this?
I know what I'm talking about.
Did you guys have it?
I'll have the A loaf of bread, please.
This one here.
That's it.
That's what Papa ate.
Mmm.
I know what you mean.
Here you go.
B's bread.
Bon appétit.
Watch this again!
Mmm! You know what?
Even if it's sudden, it's on a higher level.
I'm convinced that it's a luxury.
But I believe in myself.
This is a surprise.
Surprised?
Awwwww!
I'm kind of ripping it right there.
I almost got something wrong.
This one surprised me.
You know how I said before that you can tell when bread is fresh because of the texture, the softness of the bread.
I was so surprised by the texture.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, I said that.
It's amazing.
Why is that a word?
The Spanish were right when they said it would suddenly get a lot harder.
Have you decided? Ladies and gentlemen.
Yes, ma'am.
Which is the better fresh bread?
Yes, sir.
We're all very confident, as you said before. Can you answer that?
The better bread or the fresh bread?
Let's see.
A.
You know what I'm talking about!
One, two, three!
LOL!
Who should go this way?
Wait!
I don't know!
I don't know! I don't know! How hard can it be?
I don't know.
It was good, really good.
To be honest, the taste and texture
I wasn't sure about the taste and texture, but the smell...
The smell...
I think the phosphorus was stronger.
That's for sure.
That's the only difference.
Hmm...
I couldn't tell what it was like to eat it.
Finally...
Don't look at me, guys.
Where was your confidence?
You have to be confident.
I don't know.
I don't know. I kind of went with my favorite flavor.
Oh, I see. It's a little different.
But you have a look of despair on your face.
Awww!
Together.
Seriously, I'm not so sure about this.
Awwwww!
And if it's against my favorite thing of Ho-chan's...
Oh no!
There is a part of me that's scared.
Because we're the same.We're together.
I'm with you.
One more time.
I've finally succeeded in the first and second questions here, but...
It's time to say goodbye.
Oh no, I can't get it so nicely
So there's a tasteless Monty message...
I can't give it to someone else
Well then
I'll get right on it.
Let's jump over to the coochie shopper and tell me which one it was, please.
This is...
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm not doing it here.
Yes!
Awww.
Yay! Yay!
- Seriously? Bread! Bread!
- Red Bull of Despair
- I don't know.
- I don't know. It's actually this kind of bread.
- That's what it is.
- That's what I'm talking about.
- I see.
- Here, right here.
- Very fast slice.
Why don't you try the middle one?
Maybe on the edge.
I don't think I'd like it in the middle.
It's so soft and fluffy.
Bon appétit.
I knew the ears would be good, too.
They're sticky, too, when you touch them.
Bon appétit!
Yum!
Yes, it's delicious!
But I can't tell the texture.
Yes, it's good.
Delicious!
It tastes like rice flour.
I don't know. It's not the wheat, I don't know.
Laughs
Yes, yes, you're right, I have to see it rustled.
You're commenting more and more confidently.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Cause there's still one more.
That's right.
Next up, ladies and gentlemen, the last showdown.
You mean the third hardest?
Yeah, the hardest.
The hardest, the hardest.
But the hardest part will be the yogurt.
In the last round, we will compare Bulgarian yogurt and Akikawa Kien yogurt, both well-known yogurts!
See your reactions and guess which one you like better!
You'll see!
The first one.
It seems to be familiar, doesn't it? The one that everyone seems to be familiar with.
Yeah. No, I'll guess. It's all right.
But this is where it's going to be decided. - Right. This is where it's going to be decided.
It's the hardest part. It's so time-consuming.
I don't think it's the same.
I'm so depressed.
I'm depressed. I don't know about the end.
But I'm also a little nervous about the texture.
I'm going to work on my tongue.
I'd like to brush up on that.
But I don't want to go downhill. I've been drinking a lot of hot milk lately.
Dairy?
Dairy.
But you know, I was at a cafe recently, and I was reading all these comments about, like, real milk and Starbucks real milk, and they were talking about the difference.
They talked a lot about the difference.
I think we can do that now.
You know what I'm talking about.
I've heard about that, so...
I think it's kind of bad.
Maybe we can get a little fuzzy on this part.
If you're talking about that kind of difference.
As for the cows, I'll take care of it.
As for the cows...
If there is, by all means, have a burdock and a...
Donuts and wine!
Open your mouth.
They'll surround us with anything.
It's fun.
How fast are we going?
I don't know.
Okay, okay.
Not fast enough?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Can I go with you?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Ha-ha-ha.
You're so cute.
Eat, eat, eat?Eat and eat?
Not yet.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Yes, ma'am.
Guys, guys, guys, guys.
Let's believe in ourselves and pray.
Yes, sir.
Open a Pocky.
Daho hasn't eaten yet.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm so happy.
He's so cute.
Okay, okay.
Open a Pocky.
Delicious.
You looked a little shy just now.
Yes, but you know what?
Isn't it bad for spring?
He's a rhinoceros at first.
He might open his mouth.
So we just wait and see if he opens his mouth?
Oh, it's not open.
Let's do it.
Laugh.
I don't know... you know, when you close your eyes and people feed you things?
No, this is my first time.
It's like, wow, it's new, and it's like, wow, it's like, it clears my hearing.
It's interesting.
This picture is interesting.
Lambda, fly away!
New Makeup
Pool
Is it finished?
Yes, sir.
Wow! It's done!
Now please open it.
I see.
I've already decided on this one.
I've already decided.
Yuzuki's decided, too.
That's great.
I'm so confident.
What about you, Mar-chan?
You don't.
What's he going to do?
What kind of package is that?
It's like a long roux in here.
It's stylish.
There's a cow in here, isn't there?
At your command.
I see... I was just about to say I can pull it off now.
Well, now it's time to decide.
I'll be the final judge of whether you're a menace or not.
Yogurt.
Which was the more luxurious yogurt?
A or B?
Seino
B
I'm confused again.
A
B
Oh no.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
A-ha-ha-ha
Wait a minute.
Eeeee!
Funny!
Interesting!
I didn't know it could be so neatly divided!
On the contrary, it's amazing!
It's as amazing as the original!
Now, give us a picture of what you chose from the yuzu.
What? They're totally different?
Oh, my God.
No, it's not.
Oh! It's like, "Hello.
It's nice to meet you.
Oh, really?
My drawings are milder now, too.
It's so smooth.
This one's a little more than just...
It's not just!
Okay, Koet-chan.
B is better.
B this way?
No, B over here.
B in the nose, this way.
B in nose over here.
What did you decide?
B is better.
The one after that.
I don't think I've ever tasted anything like it.
Oh, wow.
I see.
I couldn't tell the difference either.I couldn't tell the difference either.
The atmosphere came out so much better.
The taste at the end was very deep.
I see.
Well, then...
Boo-boo, you just made cheese and grapes.
It's very interesting, but let's all go together, shall we?
Okay, let's all go now.
Which one was the luxury yogurt?
On the day of the change, which was the luxury yogurt?
Yay!
How did you know?
Oh, my God!
That's great!
So...
Honoka and Nah
Red Bull Nappy
Not Red Honobull Nappy.
It's TASTE himself!
It's Red Taste Bull Nappy!
Worst!
Taste Himself
It's Taste himself.
Really?
I have a title now.
I didn't get it.
You didn't?
I couldn't tell the difference.
I couldn't tell from the looks of it.
I like it.
Bon appétit.
Mmm, a definite winner!
Mmmm, so delicious!
LOL!
So delicious!
It's so frustrating.
Bummer?
LOL!
It's so frustrating.
It's so frustrating!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I found a new side, a side I didn't know existed.
But something, Yuzuki and Hanako, I made it into something I like
The taste I'm feeling is different.
LOL.
That's how it is.
That's what I mean.
I usually order the same menu as usual, but...
Yeah, I thought it tasted good.
It's just a different feeling, I guess.
I like it.
But it felt different.
It makes me a little sad.
You know, you said it was good even though I served it differently at the Hogusha.
Maybe.
I think he says everything is delicious.
Yeah, I think so.
It was funny.
But it was all good.
Everything was delicious.
Wow, there's a lot of good food.
It's interesting.
It was so much fun, I want to change the theme again.
I'll do it. I'll do it.
I'll do it.
I'd like to do it.
I'd like to do the same thing with you guys.
Have fun with it!
Have fun!
If you liked this video, please click the
Good Button
Comment
Subscribe to our channel
Thank you very much!
See you in the next video!
That's all.
This is SAS.
Bye bye!
Thank you very much for the food.
Здравствуйте